toplop.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy

**CONFIDENTIAL DATA NON-DISTRIBUTION AGREEMENT**

**I. General provisions**  
1\. Subject of regulation  
TopLop respects the right of members to confidentiality and will do everything possible to facilitate its non-disclosure. This Agreement determines the conditions and purposes of gathering, storing, protecting, processing and distributing information about the TopLop website.  
2\. Information, covered by the Agreement  
Information about the TopLop members includes:  
• standard data, automatically received by a http-server during access to the Site (the IP-address of the host, time, type and information about the viewing program, which requested a resource, member's operational system type, page address, from which the transition to the requested resource was done);   
• data in electronic form, provided by members during registration with the Site (members profiles - including, but not limited to: member names, logins, passwords, confidential control questions and answers, e-mail addresses, socio-metric data and the data on their preferences).   
3\. Applicable legislation  
Relationships considered in the present Agreement regarding gathering, storing, protecting, processing and distribution of information about members of the Site, are governed in accordance with the current legislation of California, not taking into account the conflict of jurisdictional requirements. By accepting the conditions of the present Agreement, you confirm your consent to consideration of a claim in the federal courts of the California district, Los Angeles City.

**II. Conditions of reference to the Site**  
TopLop assumes, that a member, addressing the Site:  
• Uses the Site on his/her own and authentically specifies personal information, when it is required;  
• Determines and has control over the settings of the software used by him/her according to his/her preferences concerning personal data protection, information about his/her own firmware and Internet connection;  
• TopLop assumes, that a member, accessing the Site is acquainted with the present Agreement and accepts its terms and conditions.

**III. Cookies Policy**  
We use cookies to keep track of some non-personal and aggregate types of information while you are visiting our website or using our services. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to our website and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save user preferences and track user behaviour, so that we can continue to develop and improve our service offering.   
You may choose to accept or reject cookies by changing your internet browser setting. However, we rely on cookies for the proper operation of our website and if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the website will not function properly. Users who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality. Click the “help” menu in your browser’s toolbar for information on how to change your settings. 

**IV. Gathering, storage, protection, processing and distribution of information**  
1\. Gathering information about members TopLop gathers information about members in accordance with the rules, determined by the present Agreement.   
2\. Restriction of information received from minors TopLop has no intention to receive information from minors. According to the Charter, TopLop forbids them using the Site.   
3\. Liability restriction for reliability of collected information  
TopLop does not verify reliability of collected information about members and does not control the legal status of members.   
4\. Storage of information about members  
TopLop gathers information about members in accordance with the rules, determined by the present Agreement. All information collected, stored and processed about members by TopLop is considered to be restricted access information.   
5\. Information protection  
TopLop undertakes all reasonable measures to protect information about its members from destruction, distortion or disclosure.   
6\. Access to information about members  
Members, interested in acquaintance, have access only to the information about other members of the Site.   
Information about other members is not accessible to the members of TopLop. An exception is made for general data, which characterize TopLop as a whole, for example, information about distribution of the members by country, age, occupation, education, etc.   
7\. Restriction of using information from members profiles TopLop uses information from members' profiles (login and password, email address) only for authorization of Internet resource access. Responsibility for the safety of the provided information is carried by the member. Any actions, conducted with the use of such information, are considered by TopLop as the actions, conducted by the member. Other information from a member's profile is not used by TopLop for distributing information to members, except for the cases stipulated by the Site usage rules, or by members' obvious inquiry.

**V. Miscellaneous**  
1\. Members' references in connection with the Agreement  
TopLop considers the references, associated with the present Agreement, including members inquiries, concerning their personal data usage, sent by the members to the following e-mail address: [info@toplop.com](mailto:info@toplop.com). Anonymous messages will not be considered.   
2\. Correspondence to the TopLop address  
All correspondence, sent by members to the TopLop address is perceived by TopLop as restricted access information and can be published only with the consent of the member. Addresses, personal data and other information about the members, who have sent these letters, cannot be used without their special consent for other purposes, but only to provide answers on the subject of a received letter.   
3\. Access to the text of the Agreement  
The present Agreement is an open and publicly accessible document. The current edition of the Agreement is placed in the Internet and has the following permanent address – <https://toplop.com/privacy.php>   
4\. TopLop right to modify the Agreement   
TopLop reserves the right to modify the present Agreement, and notify members about such modifications at the address, where the present Agreement is placed, not later than 7 days before the respective alterations will come into force. This policy was last revised on May 10, 2018.
